lakersground.net 2015-12-29

# LakersGround.net - Premier Coverage of the L.A. Lakers

  | 

**PRIVACY POLICY**

This document describes LakersGround's policies for maintaining the privacy and security of its users. This document is provided for informational purposes only and does not supersede LakersGround's [Terms of Use](http://forums.lakersground.net/faq.php#0). 

**LakersGround's Commitment to Online Security**  
LakersGround is dedicated to safeguard the security and integrity of personal information. Personal information is accessible only by site staff at the request of the user or to handle site administration duties. To protect the security of each user, each person has a unique name and password to access their information. Each user is only allowed to have one account. 

**Personal Information that LakersGround Maintains**  
LakersGround collects the following types of personal information: names, e-mail addresses and IP addresses. LakersGround may also collect business information from advertisers or web-orientated information such as website links. This information could constitute as personal information, as well as personal information from individuals acting solely in their business capacity. LakersGround caters to users of all ages. 

**How LakersGround Uses Personal Information Collected Online**  
Unless you consent, we will not use your personal information for any purpose other than that for which it is submitted. We use personal information to reply to inquiries, handle complaints, and deal with users who violate LakersGround's [Terms of Use](http://forums.lakersground.net/faq.php#0). When processing a complaint or dealing with a user who violates LakersGround's [Terms of Use](http://forums.lakersground.net/faq.php#0), we may utilize the user information to contact the individual(s) in question. Without this user information, LakersGround will not be able to process complaints and administrative duties. 

We never sell or rent your personal information. 

* LakersGround may release personal information to appropriate governmental authorities under the following circumstances: Where release is required by law (for example, a subpoena) or regulation, or is requested by a government agency conducting investigations or proceedings; 
* Where our records indicate a user may be engaged in fraudulent activity or other deceptive practices such as copyright infringement that a governmental agency should be made aware of; 
* Where your communication suggests possible harm to others. 

LakersGround uses third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

**How LakersGround protects kids' privacy**  
LakersGround complies fully with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA). We will not knowingly collect, use or distribute personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13 without prior verifiable consent from a parent or guardian. Any such information we do collect from children under the age of 13 will be used solely for internal purposes, and will not be sold or otherwise distributed to third parties. We will not knowingly allow a child under the age of 13 access to forums, private messages or other services within LakersGround that would allow them to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable information without prior verifiable consent from a parent or guardian. We will not knowingly ask a child or teen to divulge more information than is needed to participate in any LakersGround activity or service. We will not knowingly provide any direct link to Websites that are unsuitable for children or teens. 

LakersGround requires children under the age of 13 to obtain permission from their parent or guardian before sharing any personal information. User accounts registered to children under the age of 13 are disabled until LakersGround receives verifiable consent from a parent or guardian. 

**Help Us Keep Your Personal Information Accurate**  
If your personal information changes or you would like to review the personal information in the user profile, please update your information by clicking on the Edit Profile link. 

**Computer Tracking and Cookies**  
Our web sites are not set up to track, collect or distribute personal information not entered by visitors. Our site logs do generate certain kinds of non-identifying site usage data, such as the number of hits and visits to our sites. This information is used for internal purposes by technical support staff to provide better services to the public and may also be provided to others, but again, the statistics contain no personal information and cannot be used to gather such information. 

A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a Web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. LakersGround uses non-identifying cookies to provide easier site navigation and access to forums. You can still access LakersGround if your browser is set to reject cookies, but you will not be able to post on the LakersGround forums. Our cookies do not generate personal data, do not read personal data from your machine and are never tied to anything that could be used to identify you. 

**Problems or Complaints with Our Privacy Policy**  
If you have a complaint about compliance with this privacy policy, you may post a comment in the User Feedback Forum. 

If you notice any information that requires updating, please [let us know](http://forums.lakersground.net/newtopic.php?f=3).

|
